4fastfile.com 2010-06-21

# 4FastFile.com - Privacy Policy

**Logging IP Addresses**  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address. IP addresses are logged and used by 4FastFIle.com for measuring usage.

**Collecting e-mail Addresses**   
We automatically collect certain information about your computer when you visit our website, for example, the e-mail addresses of 4FastFile.com Delivery recipients and senders for the purpose of logging and measuring usage. 4FastFile.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated companies. 

**Certain Exceptional Disclosures**   
We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or in connection with any legal process. 

**Use of Cookies**   
4FastFile.com uses cookies to store the preferences and tracking trends of users. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. However, some 4FastFile.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

**File Transfer Security**   
We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Files stored for delivery are only accessible by 4FastFile.com and through the clickable link generated for your recipient. All files stored for delivery are deleted when they expire. 

**Third Party Advertising**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order not only to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you, but also to analyze, modify, and personalize advertising content on 4FastFile.com.com. We do not have access to or control over any feature they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

**Third Party Cookies**   
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**How we protect your information**   
We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. 

**External Links**   
If any part of the 4FastFile.com website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. 4FastFile.com may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

**How you can contact us**   
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at 

_legal@4FastFile.com._

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, we will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints.
